ANDREI GARCIA CUADRA



Leganes, Madrid (Spain)

21-11-1997 (**21 years**)

Started on IT with 10 years.

Started programming with 12 years.

Love to read n' dance.

"Best programmers are those who has the most soft-skills, so whole team is gonna be as good as you can be, and get your hard-skills thought it."

https://bitbucket.org/ d3sd1/

https://github.com/ d3sd1

Profile

Leadership and excellence. I'm focused on excellence and not on single results: it can always be better. I love coding and creativeness, not recurrent tasks, and I'm full stack developer, system manager, system analyst, system integrations, IOT, DevOps and designer. All I imagine is everything I learn.

I worked on so many companies since I was freelance and I establish many of. Although I work on multiples at same time.

Experience

[Hidden name], Madrid - 2018-Present

Founder of startup [Hidden name due to company constitution] online marketplace. Real time systems, testing, Spring boot 5, Angular 8, Hibernate, Flyway...

Workout Events, Madrid — 2018-Present

Leadership programmer, DevOps, Tester, BackEnd, FrontEnd, Bots, System's Integration. Programmed mainly on PHP and Symfony...

Iberforma, Remote - 2018-Present

Leadership programmer of e-learning platform. Only IT person on 100+ employees company. Critical systems, Moodle, Ubuntu, Aqua CRM integrations...

Freelance, Remote - 2013-Present

Minor jobs that were just about some hours and few money. Moodle modules, Wordpress, Spring fixes, NodeJS optimisations, AngularJS/Angular2+ miniapps...

ICM Online courses, Remote - 2019

Temporal programmer for some needed modules of e-learning platform. Integration with an external ERP and so many modules.

Soluzink, Remote - 2017-2019

Founder of startup Soluzink. It was an online video chat for psychologist to work on with this platform. It had video-chat, user manage, UX/UI, and real time data. Discarded due to team disruption.

SCM Night, Remote — 2017-2019

Founder of startup SCM Night. It was an offline application that could control any room with NFC card integration, country card decryption and so many statistics on real time. Built with Angular 4 and PHP websockets.

Education

Carlos III University, Madrid, Spain — Computing Technology, Present Enrique Tierno Galvan, Madrid, Spain - Web programming, 2018 ESIC, Madrid, Spain - Marketing computing, 2018 Jung School, Madrid, Spain — Neuro-linguistic programming, 2018 Luis vives, Madrid, Spain - Hardware n' Networks, 2016 Town Hall, Madrid, Spain - Social monitor, 2015 Julio Verne, Madrid, Spain - Basic school, 2014

References

I got some recommendation letters from teachers and bosses. You can find them on my personal website. You can find everything (also contact me) through my website.

Skills (Verbose n' cut off).

- FrontEnd:

- iQuery 3, 2, 1.
- Angular 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 2.
- Nebular.
- Vanilla JavaScript.
- TypeScript.
- Dart.
- NativeScript.
- [Ask for more, I learn too fast].

- BackEnd:

- Java 12,11,10, 9, 8, 7.
- Java EE 12, 8, 7.
- PHP 7, 5, 4.
- ASP.net.
- Web frameworks (Symfony, Struts...).
- Node.JS.
- Python.
- Spring.
- SQL (MySql, MariaDB).
- PL/SQL.
- NO-SQL (MongoDB).
- ORM (Doctrine, Hibernate...).
- [Ask for more, I learn too fast].

- Others:

- Wordpress.
- Version control (Glt, Mercurial).
- Team manager (ClickUp, Trello).
- Joomla.
- Moodle.
- IntelliJ, NetBeans, Eclipse, Visual Studio. Unix Kernel (MacOS, Mint, Ubuntu, CentOS, RedHat).
- Cloud computing services (AWS, Google Cloud...).
- Network manager.
- Designer w/ responsive (Photoshop, Bootstrap, Material, Materialize...).
- Services manager (Nginx, SSH, Apache, dovecot, [big etc here]...).
- [Ask for more, I learn too fast].